<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>Trippy Stuff</title>
  <link>http://www.w3schools.com</link>
  <description>A collection of randomly trippy and psychadelic stories by G3n3r0</description>
  <item id="bullying">
    <title>Bullying</title>
    <link>http://cloud9ide.com/g3n3r0/online_os/workspace/trippyStuff.xml#bullying</link>
    <description>
    <![CDATA[
    Alfonze came up to me. He took out a shiv that he had whittled. He stabbed at me, rupturing my kidney. I quickly responded, throwing an autodidactic grenade into his mouth. There was an Explosion, followed by Darkness.<br />
    When I awoke, I was in a dimly lit room. A sticky Substance covered the ground. I pusillanimously pulled myself to my feet. I began sinking into the slick, cucumbery Substance. I leveled my body out again, and felt myself gliding upwards like ocotpodes through pink Jello. I regained buoyancy, and took in a deep braeth of the peppermint Wind. I glided through the Substance like a butterfly. Suddenly, gamboge Lights flickered beneath me. A shimmering aquadillo lept from beneath the semisolid liquid. There was no ripple, it just seemed to pass beyond the surface. It made a sound like the air passing through an x-ray rainbow in Xanadu. The aquadillo then went back through the substance as it had come, but a sound like breaking glass danced upon my ears. More aquadillos began leaping through the air. They joined me in swimming, and soon I didn't know who was following who. I saw a glimmering, ultraviolet light up ahead, and saw the aquadillos swim away. I stood up, and felt solid ground beneath my feet. In the light, I could see ancient statues of Kubla Khan and his likenesses faintly outlined. Slowly, I walked into the light.<br />
    I fell out of one of the many pinhole cameras dotting the school like tiny aphids on a quivering blade of grass in a flickering, bat-filled field. I landed face-first on one of the deflated bean-bag chairs with a loud thump. The disgruntled librarian gave me an angry look, and then proceeded to shush me.
    ]]>
    Alfonze came up to me.
    </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2011</pubDate>
  </item>
</channel>

</rss>